I couldn't screenshot it — Playwright installed but its browser download sits outside the sandbox's network allowlist — so this went through code review plus three headless walks instead. Worth your eye on the real thing.

PDF → bank
bash
python3 tools/pdf_to_bank.py exam.pdf -o data/my-bank.json

The part that makes it work: NITE prints אנלוגיות (שאלות 1-6) above each run, so item types are read, not guessed. Page headers give domain and chapter, the מפתח תשובות נכונות page gives the answer key. Hebrew comes out of pdftotext with mirrored punctuation — (1) arrives as )1( — so the parser expects both forms.

On a fixture built from your booklet: 13/13 answers correct, all types, all three domains, locked in as tools/test_parser.py.

What it won't do: passage and figure bodies. Reading questions get wired to a stimulus stub flagged for review, and you paste the passage in. Multi-column layouts scramble prose badly enough that auto-extraction would quietly corrupt it — a corrupted passage is worse than an empty one. Everything else uncertain lands in the JSON as a 'review' field rather than a silent guess.

Your PDF wasn't on disk this session (only its text reached me), so run it against the real file and send me the --report output if the headers don't match — that hook is one regex in DOMAIN_HEADERS.

Two bugs the tests caught along the way: the length selector was resetting itself on every re-render, and one of my own assertions was wrong rather than the code (body.textContent includes inline script source).
